Choose an operation to perform on the data:
1. Arrange movies by release_date
2. Filter out only movies with rating over 7.5
3. Print the movies highest and lowest revenue (not 0)
e. Exit
Enter your choice (1-3 or e): 
********************************************************

Highest revenue movie:
Name: Avatar, Revenue: 2781505847

Lowest revenue movie (not 0):
Name: Shattered Glass, Revenue: 2

********************************************************

Choose an operation to perform on the data:
1. Arrange movies by release_date
2. Filter out only movies with rating over 7.5
3. Print the movies highest and lowest revenue (not 0)
e. Exit
Enter your choice (1-3 or e): Exiting.
